<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SCiP</title>
    <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SCiP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Announcements</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/announcements/</guid>
      <description>Society for Computation in Psychology. A forum for cutting-edge methods for the psychological sciences since 1971. Computation, information, technology, statistics, applications and more!
You can view our previous emails to the society using this link.
2023 Conference Information Thanks for attending the conference!
 2023 Student Award Information Castellan winners have been announced! Check out the awards page.
 Special Section of Behavior Research Methods View the collection
Conference presenters (both spoken and poster presentations) are invited to submit articles based on presentations at the SCiP meeting to a special section of Behavior Research Methods, the official journal of the Society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Information</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/conference/</guid>
      <description>2023 Conference Information Thank you all for attending SCiP and see you next year in NYC!
 Program  Pay Conference Fee The 53rd annual meeting of the Society for Computation in Psychology (SCiP) is pleased to announce its call for abstracts. The meeting will be held on Thursday, November 16, 2023, before the opening of the annual meeting of the Psychonomic Society. We will be holding this event in person in San Francisco in tandem with the Psychonomic Society Meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/governance/</guid>
      <description>President and Directorship  President: Caitlin Mills, University of Minnesota President-Elect: Shelia Kennison, Oklahoma State University Executive Director: Erin Buchanan, Harrisburg University   Steering Committee  2021-2024: Xiaowei Zhao, Emmanuel College 2022-2025: Ulf-Dietrich Reips, University of Konstanz 2022-2025: Brendan Johns, McGill University 2022-2025: Mitchell Dandignac, Stanford University 2023-2026: Katie McCarthy, Georgia State University 2024-2027: Stephen Hutt, University of Denver 2024-2027: Alex Paxton, University of Connecticut 2024-2027: Nicholas Maxwell, Midwestern State University  Click here for SCiP’s bylaws</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of SCiP</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/history/</guid>
      <description>In 1971, Donald Tepas, then at St. Louis University, contacted the National Science Foundation with a request for support in developing an interactive system for searches. The NSF representative Tepas looked into the possibility of arranging a conference and publishing the proceedings. The first meeting was so successful that the meetings have been held ever since! The logo featured on our homepage.
The Society for Computation in Psychology (SCiP) was previously known as the National Conference on the Use of On-Line Computers in Psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCiP Awards</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/awards/</guid>
      <description>Castellan Prize SCiP’s primary annual award is the The John Castellan Student Paper Award for the most outstanding student paper. Student papers on the application of computational or computerized methods to any area of psychology (theoretical, experimental, applied) are welcome. Eligibility is open to work done by a student currently enrolled in undergraduate or graduate courses, or work done as part of a course, thesis, or other student research by a person who graduated within the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
