<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SCiP</title>
    <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SCiP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcements</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/announcements/</guid>
      <description>Society for Computation in Psychology. A forum for cutting-edge methods for the psychological sciences since 1971. Computation, information, technology, statistics, applications and more!
You can view our previous emails to the society using this link.
Conference Information The Annual Meeting of the Society for Computation in Psychology (SCiP) takes place one day before the main conference of the Psychonomic Society. SCiP 2021 will be held as a virtual event on November 4th from 8:00 - 5:00 PM Central Time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Information</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/conference/</guid>
      <description>2021 Conference Details The Annual Meeting of the Society for Computation in Psychology (SCiP) takes place one day before the main conference of the Psychonomic Society. SCiP 2021 will be held as a virtual event on November 4th from 8:00 - 5:00 PM Central Time.
The theme for this year’s conference is 50 Years of Computation. As the world increasingly relies on computation, we look back to the advances and innovations from psychology and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/governance/</guid>
      <description>President and Directorship  President: Pietro Cipresso, University of Turin President-Elect: TBA Executive Director: Erin Buchanan, Harrisburg University Executive Director: Rick Dale, UCLA   Steering Committee  2018-2021: Stephanie Huette, The University of Memphis 2018-2021: Kay Livesay, Linfield College 2021-2024: Xiaowei Zhao, Emmanuel College 2021-2024: Caitlin Mills, University of New Hampshire  Click here for SCiP’s bylaws
 Past Presidents  2020: Alexandra Paxton, University of Connecticut 2019: Danielle McNamara, Arizona State University 2018: Chris Westbury, University of Alberta 2017: Xiaowei Zhao, Emmanuel College 2016: Randy Jamieson, University of Manitoba 2015: Peter Dixon, University of Alberta 2014: Kay Livesay, Linfield College 2013: Michael Jones, Indiana University 2012: Ping Li, Pennsylvania State University 2011: Joseph P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of SCiP</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/history/</guid>
      <description>In 1971, Donald Tepas, then at St. Louis University, contacted the National Science Foundation with a request for support in developing an interactive system for searches. The NSF representative Tepas looked into the possibility of arranging a conference and publishing the proceedings. The first meeting was so successful that the meetings have been held ever since! The logo featured on our homepage.
The Society for Computation in Psychology (SCiP) was previously known as the National Conference on the Use of On-Line Computers in Psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCiP Awards</title>
      <link>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://society-for-computation-in-psychology.github.io/awards/</guid>
      <description>Castellan Prize SCiP’s primary annual award is the The John Castellan Student Paper Award for the most outstanding student paper. Student papers on the application of computational or computerized methods to any area of psychology (theoretical, experimental, applied) are welcome. Eligibility is open to work done by a student currently enrolled in undergraduate or graduate courses, or work done as part of a course, thesis, or other student research by a person who graduated within the past year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>